OYEBAMIJI, MUSTAPHA OYETUNDE

Tel: +2349076109309 | Email: oyebamijimustapha44@gmail.com

Website: https://musoye.github.io | Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/musoye

Github: https://www.github.com || Developer Blog: https://musoye.hashnode.dev/

SUMMARY

I am a trained Full Stack Developer and self-trained Technical Writer, I'm a purpose-driven individual; quick to adapt to any learning environment; possess human relation skill, interpersonal skill ,encapsulate it with creative, and writing skill; I'm also equipped with researching skill and certified with knowledge in crowd-funding. As a self-motivated and impact-driven individual, over the year I have gained Frontend web development skills which include HTML, CSS, JavaScript programming language and ability to use Bootstrap to style website; Backend Web development skills which include using Flask and Django framework for building backend architecture; Database skill includes MySQL, PostgreSQL, and SQLAlchemyORM for database management, and other tools and skills which includes Graphic Designing, Git / Github, Python and C Programming Language, Linux, and Technical Writing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ALX SWE - INTERNSHIP

August 2022 - Present

- One-year Software Engineering Training.
- A comprehensive guide on System Designing.
- Technical Writing Skill.
- Collaboration Skill.
- Website: https://www.alxafrica.com

ZURI TRAINING – INTERSHIP

April 2022 - August 2022

- > Full-stack Development Skill
- Collaboration Skill
- Website: https://www.zuri.team
- Certificate verification: https://waiting.zuriboard.com/certificate/verify/5/i4g0121456zv

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATION

Senior Secondary School Certificate(7 Distinctions, 2 Credits)

Olivet Baptist High School, Oyo, Oyo State, Nigeria.

CERTIFICATIONS

- JavaScript Data Structure and Algorithm FreeCodeCamp, org. 2022
 (https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc51a0a427-b3ee-4016-84f5-aceea585c446/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures)
- Full Stack Development Zuri Training, 2022.

(https://waiting.zuriboard.com/certificate/verify/5/i4g0121456zv)

- Secondary School Leaving Testimonial Olivet Baptist High School, Oyo, Oyo State, Nigeria. 2021
- Graphic Designing, Video Editing, and Basics of Marketing *Techyscholarsng* (SDS4S) 2022
- Crowd Funding HP ONLINE COURSE
- Confirm All below: (https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1Q4wtV_ZmpbQfC3WgKq2SlZxd2-PqgXKb)

LEADERSHIP ROLE

▶ Member Academic Excellence (ACADEX) Club.
(Tutor/Mentor)
Olivet Baptist High School, Oyo.
2018 – 2021

Responsibilities

- Trained Junior Colleagues on Manner of Inculcating Knowledge.
- Tutored junior colleagues in subjects not limited to Chemistry, Further Mathematics, Mathematics and Physics.
- Recorded more than 90% improvement in their academic performance.

ACADEMIC RECORDS

- Overall Best Graduating student, Olivet Baptist High School, Oyo, 2021 set. -2021
- Best Graduating Student in Science Class by National Old Student Association (NOSA) class of 1999 2021.
- Award of Excellence in Mathematics as Best Graduating Student in Mathematics by NOSA(1983-1988 set) 2021.
- 1st position in Muslim Student Society of Nigeria (MSSN) quiz competition organized at Sped International, Oyo -
- 329/400 in Unified Tertiary Matriculation Board Examination (UTME) top 0.06% of people who scored above 300 in 2021.

RESEARCH AND PROJECT

- An E-commerce Website with Shopping cart and Payment integration (https://musta.netlify.app/)
- A Web Dictionary (https://dictmus.netlify.app/)
- Built a Simple Bourne Shell (https://github.com/Musoye/simple_shell)
- Built an Interpreter (monty) (https://github.com/Musoye/monty)
- A School Portal for Students (https://github.com/Musoye/StudentPortal/)
- Contributed to Clovar cms(team 15) in Zuri Intership (https://clovarcms.herokuapp.com)
- Write a Blog post on Redirecting Python Standard Output (https://musoye.hashnode.dev/redirecting-standard-output-using-io-and-sys-module-python)

TRAINING/ CONFERENCE ATTENDED

- Islamic Vocational Course by Istijabah Prayer Group of Nigeria (IPGON), 2014.
- Sensitization And Awareness on Importance of Studying Statistics and Mathematics by Royal Statistical Societyof Nigeria local group and Department of Mathematical Science of Ajayi Crowther University, Oyo State Nigeria, 17th March, 2020.

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

- Fellow @theroom. (https://www.theroom.com/)
 Ambassadorship by SMART NETWORK.
- Junior Engineers Technicians and Scientist Club (JETS CLUB)